Take care of my sister for me.
Brigade Commander.
This Browning
is a pair with the one on your desk.
When I was in Chongqing,
when I was in Chongqing.
I gave her one when I found my sister.
I kept it with me.
It's yours now.
Thank you, Brigade Commander.
Go ahead.
Take care, Brigade Commander.
Done.
Thank you. Put it on.
Where did you get this gun?
Your brother gave it to me.
My brother
He said thank you for protecting you.
Colonel.
This is the list of candidates selected in Shanzhou.
You can be
a seed translator.
If you think it's suitable,
please sign here.
I'll arrange a training task immediately.
It's very important
is very important.
It can be planted everywhere.
to gather information for us.
You can show us the way
when the army sweeps.
At the same time, we can control the activities of the guerrilla team.
Mr. Pang.
Yes.
Thank you for your help.
It’s my duty.
Have a good rest, Colonel.
Colonel.
Tachihara-kun!
How is your injury?
He hurt one of his arms.
Soldiers of the empire are loyal to the emperor. They are not afraid of death.
One arm is nothing.
It's just a telegram from General Kurokawa.
What did General Kurokawa say?
He scolded us so badly.
He said because the Imperial Army was kidnapped,
due to the abduction of the royal army.
was suspended.
You and I are sinners of Yamato!
You want me to borrow a wrong knife from you
to commit suicide.
Colonel, don't be too anxious.
We need to choose
a safer route.
After seven days,
after seven days.
Mr. Tanihara, you're right.
But in these three mountain,
are surrounded by guerrilla team.
Where is the safe route?
These problems are indeed tricky.
But there's a way.
Since it doesn't work on land,
let's go to the sky.
The sky?
Don't we have an airport?
Please ask General Kurokawa
to transfer a plane from Fuyang.
We’ll take the gold from the sky.
I don’t believe the guerrilla team can still get it.
Tawahara-san, you're so smart.
Good.
Colonel, have a good rest.
I'll send a telegram now.
Thank you, Mr. Tanihara.
Yes.
Great Lord, we've been busy all morning.
We finally have time to rest.
Sit down.
Let's have some hot tea.
Very good.
Have some tea.
Buddy, lend me a light.
I think we've driven them crazy.
He tried to transport it in the air.
You want to use my airport?
Dream on.
from Shaanxi to Luoyang.
Although the transportation cost is high,
but the safety is very reliable.
It's not far from the mine to the airport.
As long as the kids are on guard,
it's very unfavorable to us.
They blew up the airport.
and cut off their transport route.
But what about the gold mine?
As long as we don't destroy the gold mine,
there will be endless gold production.
Even if we blow up the airport,
we can still
in other ways.
You keep talking about the gold mine.
But we...
we have come up with
a better way
A perfect way, right?
Brother.
I wonder if I can say something.
Say it.
Aren't we discussing war? Say it.
I think
you just don't want to build the airport
to be occupied by the enemy.
That's why I'm determined to attack it.
But the airport is heavily guarded.
If something goes wrong,
your independent Brigade is very dangerous.
You underestimated your brother.
Wen Kui.
No one underestimated you.
Come, sit down.
Hurry up.
Yes.
Well, I admit
I'm selfish.
But I'm a professional soldier.
Right?
I have a lot of combat experience.
Before the war,
I analyzed
Right?
So I...
Right, Li?
Yes.
No one denies you.
How about this?
Since you think both things
are very important,
Let's split up
to take down the airport and the mine.
and have a good rest.
What do you think?
I think what Shangguan Eagle said is right.
Split up the troops.
Will it affect our attack on the gold mine and airport?
They have heavily guarded.
Since it's a surprise attack,
It's an unexpected attack.
It's not about the number of offensive players.
but our tactics are accurate.
Win with the less and win with the weak.
Now the idea of steamed buns is
are more and more alike.
We've been fighting each other since childhood.
Now it seems that we're getting more and more in sync.
Choi Moon-Kui.
In the fight,
we've always had a tacit understanding.
Okay.
Let's split up.
I want to check the mine
to see if I can find
to quickly evacuate the people.
If anything happens,
we won't be passive.
Sure.
We'll go on a field survey then.
It's settled then.
I'm going back to the unit.
and ask my brothers to prepare some ammunition.
to repair
fix it again.
Wait for my news.
I'm counting on you.
Hurry up.
What is it?
Mr. Liu.
Xu.
when are we going to take action?
Miss and Captain Cai.
Do you have any news?
They are still discussing.
The plan must be careful.
Otherwise, we'll have to pay a huge price.
Even if they blow up the gold mine,
the people may not be able to leave alive.
That's true.
The kid has been pushing us hard these days.
Everyone can't help it.
I'm worried.
they would torture me
before they died.
If I'm not mistaken,
the captain’s plan
will come out soon.
Let everyone wait for another day or two.
I'll let you know
I'll inform you immediately.
Okay.
I will comfort everyone.
I believe Miss Leng and Captain Cai
won't leave us alone.
Yes.
They won't leave you behind.
Let everyone get ready.
to survive.
We will see the light soon.
Fuyang called.
General Kurokawa has agreed to our request.
Three days later,
in three days.
Three days? That's too fast.
Looks like General Kurokawa is really anxious.
How many days do we need for the interview?
Can we complete the mission to load the gold in time?
Please rest assured, Colonel.
I'll ask the miners to work overtime.
I promise to be on standby in three days.
When the plane lands,
when the plane lands.
I believe in
in your efficiency.
I’m just worried about the guerrilla team.
They are ambushing on the way.
These guerrilla teams
are so cunning.
[He's full of tricks.]
I fell into their trap.
Gosh.
Damn it!
Don't worry, Colonel.
Colonel just needs to sweep the transport line repeatedly
and kick them out of the three levels,
they won't be a problem.
I think the mine and airport
are their real target.
My soldiers are stationed in these two places.
Ranger team won’t touch stones with eggs.
Colonel just said
No. 8 guerrilla is as cunning as a fox.
We have to guard against them.
That's right, Tawahara-san.
If they attack us,
we're not prepared.
if we don't prepare.
Take good care of the mine these days.
I'll send more people to guard the airport.
I won't give them a chance.
I'll get going then.
Major.
Mr. Pang.
How long have you been here?
Just a while ago.
I heard you were discussing business with Colonel.
so I didn't dare to knock on the door.
Mr. Pang, come in.
Yes.
Excuse me, Major Tanaka.
I couldn't find a decent road.
I've almost forgotten what I've been through.
Don't worry.
The paths we walked are all in my mind.
Look.
Isn't that a mine?
I didn't expect
we found a good observation spot.
This place
It reminds me of something better than the observation position.
What is it?
After all, if we blow up the mine,
after the kids clean up,
we'll catch another batch of people to continue our investigation.
But if we flood this mine,
it'll be different.
Look at the location of the lake.
is right above the mine.
If we put more explosives
in the lake,
and create a big crack.
When the lake seeps out,
the valley will be flooded instantly.
By then,
it'll be hard
it'll be hard.
Good idea.
It can also avoid
a lot of casualties caused by a direct attack.
And even if the lake recedes,
the soil will become soft.
This place is not suitable to start anymore.
Even if this mine is completely destroyed,
I'll do as you say.
Let's go.
Here.
Xu, the situation has changed.
I have to find a way to contact Comrade Tsai.
Please inform them for me.
It's urgent.
Hurry up, Xu.
Don't move.
I didn't expect
Mr. Pang is young
but he's so shrewd.
You've been hiding
for so long.
but we didn't notice it.
You seem to be diligent,
working for our army.
but secretly sent the message to the guerrilla team.
Including that time in Fuyang City,
you were able to escape
must be your work.
You've calculated two things.
The rescue of people in Luoyang Prison
and the gold transportation truck.
was also sent by me.
I really admire you.
But do you think I'm that stupid?
I failed again and again.
If I don't find the real mastermind,
I, Masahio Tahara,
can't report to His Majesty.
So you suspected me long ago.
Congratulations, Mr. Tanaka.
However,
you won't get anything from me.
Really?
Okay.
I want to see how hard your bones are.
Take him back.
Mr. Pang.
You're not being smart.
Ants are still alive.
If you don't try hard,
you can't say no easily.
That makes sense.
Human instinctive reaction is the most real.
I want to see
to save your life.
Old friend, we meet again.
Why are you here?
The Japanese are very strict now.
Every Chinese who works for them
who work for them.
Even our investigation team has to explain
who we have dealt with.
Without contact with strangers,
how can you catch our guerrilla team?
How to get information?
Captain Choi, stop joking.
I’m so nervous that I’m sweating.
The investigation is so strict.
because the Japanese
caught a commie spy.
He's quite something.
I heard that
he was trusted by General Kurokawa.
and helped Colonel Matsui translate.
He is in charge of
in the west.
Where is he locked up?
How can we do it?
We're here for him.
Don't even think about him.
He's locked up in the Japanese headquarters.
Not to mention you,
I can't even fly in.
Stop boasting for the kid.
You can't even fly in?
Our men
sent out the information.
Fine, forget it.
I was wrong.
Show us around the Japanese Command Center.
Don't cause any more trouble.
The Japanese are crazy now.
We've suffered a lot.
Don't hit the gun.
Bao.
How about
Since you're here,
we have to go on a field inspection.
Otherwise, how can we explain to our brothers?
Take us there.
Really?
Let's go.
Okay.
I'm not lying, am I?
The Japanese have been very strict lately.
I'm afraid their mission will be leaked again.
Even the shops nearby
were forced to close.
Indeed.
Even if we can get into the Command Center,
we'll get caught soon.
Not to mention bringing people out,
you'll even lose yourself.
Go to the back.
I really want to go in!
and kill them all.
I understand how you feel.
But at this moment,
we need to calm down.
Once we lose our mind,
the whole guerrilla team
will face great danger.
Yes, Captain Cai.
It’s never too late to take revenge.
Watching his comrade suffer heavy punishment,
only a wall away,
but we can't save him.
How can I bear it?
We have to endure it now.
You're not the only one who is loyal.
We are all sacrificing for the anti-Japanese.
Let's go to the tea shop first.
Go to the tea shop.
Pang is an experienced
with a lot of experience.
It's not time to meet him.
He would rather risk his life to go to the tea shop.
It means there's something that must be delivered.
You mean
Pang will put the information in the tea shop?
I worked with Pang for a while.
He's very flexible.
He might leave us some clues.
Okay.
Let's go.
If there is any information,
we need to find it as soon as possible.
It's too late.
Someone might find out about the information.
Yes, let's go.
I didn't expect someone from the special class to come.
Yes.
Now,
we'll be in trouble.
If we can't enter the tea shop,
we can't get any information.
On the contrary, they might have it.
Bo-ra Chae, should I try?
You...
Yes.
I was afraid of death,
because I was afraid of death.
But I'm also Chinese.
I followed you all the way.
I heard what you said.
When I was with Huo Lang,
with Huo Lang.
Now that you're the Chief of Investigation,
I've been following them to do evil things.
I'm living a miserable life.
like a ghost.
I'm also worried about the Japanese.
I'm afraid he would be killed
he will be executed.
Jennifer Cai.
I don’t dare to say the sacrifice.
Let me do it.
Okay.
Take care.
Okay, I'm going.
Stop!
Police, help the Royal Army with the investigation.
Let's go.
Tachihara-san!
Tai Jun.
What are you doing here?
Tachihara-san.
I heard the royal army solved a spy case.
I'm here to help the Royal Army.
This is a special lesson.
It's none of your business.
Go back.
But...
But what?
Do you want me to repeat it again?
No, no, yes.
Yes.
The Japanese doesn't trust Chinese at all.
Since we can't get in,
let's go back to the base and discuss.
That's all we can do.
Let's go.
Wen Pei, look what this is.
This is the nail bone writing.
It says three days.
The last word seems to be an unfinished word.
This is the information Pang left.
It means
the Japanese will transport gold on the third day.
Without today,
we only have two days left.
We need to go back and get ready.
When Pang was in danger,
when he was in danger.
So we can't let him down.
so that he won't die in vain.
Comrades,
Captain Cai and I
made a very important decision.
to give up the plan to save Pang.
to attack the mine and airport.
The Japanese transported the gold earlier.
They are going to Luoyang the day after tomorrow.
We don't have much time left.
If we take action,
Pang
for the devil.
This is the hardest decision
made the most difficult decision.
But we have no choice.
The country is in danger.
I have to go and carry on.
to sacrifice yourself
is the best way to repay Pang.
Guys.
Pang sent this message with his life.
We can't let his blood go in vain.
We must complete the mission.
We can't let the devil take one tael of gold away.
That's the wealth of our Chinese.
We'd rather destroy it
than make it
to harm our compatriots.
We planned to split into two groups.
From the source to the transport process,
from the source to the transportation of gold.
But I'm worried that after Pang's incident,
after Pang's incident.
The airport is no compared to the forest.
Their heavy weapons
will cause great damage to us.
Independent Brigade
on fire.
That's right.
I'm still confident.
But now,
a squadron has been added.
If that's the case,
Unless...
Unless we're determined to die.
No.
Even if we have all our men,
we might not be able to take the airport.
So I plan to contact my superiors
to send someone
to help us attack the airport.
Good idea.
I heard that the Eight Army
to Shanzhou and the treasure.
It's not too late to send someone now.
We need to choose a suitable candidate.
Eagle and I will lead the team.
to help attack the airport.
No clones.
Comrade Choi Mun-bae will be in charge too.
Saving the mine workers and destroying the mine.
The mission is also very difficult.
Now let's see
who can complete the mission.
Bao, I'll blow up the dam.
I can't escape.
Although I'm suitable,
but I need to contact Wu Qiusheng.
so that we can cooperate with Mr. Cui
and save the people.
Let me recommend someone.
My adjutant.
He has been with me for so many years. I can rest assured of him.
And my trusted subordinate
Lieutenant Zhu is bold and meticulous.
It's best for sending information.
Thank you, Lieutenant Zhu.
I'll do anything to fight the Japanese.
Don't embarrass me.
Yes.
After the meeting,
after the meeting.
When you arrive at the station of the Eight Army,
tell them our plan.
and ask them to come here as soon as possible.
I'll complete the mission.
Why aren't you eating?
I'm thinking about what you said.
If you miss me,
you really have a plan.
One, two, three, four, five.
Everything is perfect.
I feel that no matter how hard the mission is,
no matter how hard the mission is.
But you know me.
I do things based on my feelings.
I tend to be careless.
In the past,
my father helped me.
Now I bring my swordsman
Sometimes I feel a little weak.
Don't be too harsh on yourself.
As long as you're human,
there's something I can't do.
Just say me.
Not everything
can be calculated.
Plans can't catch up with changes.
Just like when I came to Sandao Akira for a mission,
Meeting you
is the biggest accident in my life.
You made me more clear
why I fight.
Sometimes,
The reason for fighting is simple.
To protect the one you love,
and avenge the dead.
and live for the living.
That thought has been hidden in my heart.
I can't accept the torn pain.
I forced myself to stick to it.
Even if I'm smashed to pieces.
It gives me courage
to face all difficulties.
We've known each other for so long.
for the first time.
I used to think
we have plenty of time and opportunities to talk about it.
But the battle the day after tomorrow
is extremely dangerous.
No one knows what will happen.
So, I want to tell you everything.
Don't you have confidence in this battle?
Confidence is different from accidents.
It doesn't matter.
I just don't want any regrets.
Let's wait until we win.
If anything happens,
tell me on the way to hell.
I won't forget
I won't forget.
Comrade Peng Tao is right.
Fight and love can be equal.
The more important it is,
the more I think the time I spend with you is precious.
Listen, Cai.
I will marry you in my life.
Whether you're alive or dead,
or disabled,
Nothing can separate us.
Look at this road.
Does it look like the road
when we were young?
At that time, the three of us...
You, me, Bao.
So naughty.
He always comes out at night
in the pool
and catch their frogs.
and catch fireflies.
and eat other people's food.
and do something unreasonable.
Father will beat us when he catches us.
Twenty years have passed.
I don't know what home is like.
After we defeat the kids,
we’ll go back to Peking together.
Then we can sort out
the abandoned yard
and add new soil to my father's grave.
When we go back,
if we go back.
Yes, Shangguan Eagle.
Uncle Cai
can rest in peace.
I'm not talking about Shangguan Eagle.
Are you pretending?
I'm talking about the Cui family.
Should I add a pair of chopsticks?
What are you talking about?
We've never confessed our feelings.
How would I know?
You're blushing.
Why should I confess?
Lower your voice.
You're following me around every day.
It's almost on the bottom.
But
your brother thinks this is good.
It's called the spirit of knights in the west.
It's better than those weak.
Although your brother is a little jealous,
but
I think it's reliable.
Wait.
Hey.
Let me ask you.
after the war,
will you go back to Pei
with Wen Pei?
I'll listen to Brigade Commander.
Don't call me Brigade Commander.
I'm no longer a military.
Like this.
Let me put it this way.
If
as a future brother-in-law,
as my future brother-in-law.
Will you?
What do you think?
This can give my father an explanation.
Where is Wen Pei going?
Where am I going?
What did you say? Say it again!
Say it again.
Fly on the boat.
You're a famous swordsman.
Are you embarrassed now?
Did you hear that?
Brother, are you done?
No.
Did you hear what he said?
Where is Wen Pei going?
Where am I going?
Stop it.
Alright.
It's too cold here. I can't stay here.
Take good care of her.
Your brother-in-law is watching you.
I have to go. I have to go back to the camp.
Take care, Brigade Commander.
Take care of her.
Remember, I'm watching you.
Everyone.
Everyone,
tomorrow will be an important day.
It concerns the victory
of our Japanese army.
Please prepare enough weapons and ammunition.
Come down the mountain with me tomorrow morning.
and go straight to the Toad Cave to escort the gold.
Yes!
Ranger army of the Eight Army.
is our biggest enemy.
They'll definitely attack us
to attack us.
Please don't fight.
Don't fall into their trap.
Remember your duty as transport.
After this,
I will definitely celebrate for you.
It's our honor to serve the empire.
We will not let
of Major Tanaka.
I'm counting on you.
Yes.
Leader He.
Major.
Please take care of
to take care of us.
Mr. He has contributed a lot
for the Japanese.
When I return the gold,
I will return your daughter as promised.
I'll let you reunite
and enjoy the happiness of the family.
Thank you, Major Tanihara.
Go.
Yes.
[Choi Bo-wol]
Choi Bo-wol.
and actors.
Su Tianhui, Yang Wanlin, Zhao Dongliang, Chen Yile, Wang Lusheng.
Yue, Wang, Yang Ziyi, Tian Chenzhe, Deng Kai. Mei Liang Dong.
Li Yishuo Yu Hongda Tian Guofeng Gong
to perform.
Liu, Tong, Wang, Liu Jiawen, Sun, Jin, Wang Yukun.
Zhang Hongbo, Gong Jianfeng, Li Kaiwu, Zhuang, Tao Sun Haochun.
Xu Fu, Wu Jianyu, Zhang Guangyan, Sun Yuanwen Chang, Qing.
Xu Da Gu Chen Chen Wei Jie Liu
Li Jinyang Zhang Jianing Liu Rong Qi
Li Xichen Zhao Jianhao Li Xiaoyan Dong Qisun
Chen Weigui, Wang Qinghua, Wang Qingyong, Zhao Minjie
Wang Qingyu, Feng Qimeng, Chen Weiwei, Peng Peng, Ji, Yan Qing.
Staff table.
Director team.
The production team.
Photography team.
Sun Linfei.
Lighting Team.
Cao Peihu.
The clothing team.
The dressing team.
Zhao Yang.
Art team.
Props team.
Vice-captain of the props, Cui Guangzang.
Team leader, Yang Longfei.
Action team.
Fireworks.
The gun team.
The recording team.
The venue team.
Driver team.
Li Zhenmin, Dou Xingbin, Rong Xijun.
Wei Zidian, Qiao Chunsheng, Yang, Tao, Chen Jianfen Jiang Jiping.
Wang Bao Cheung, Su Gao Feng, Liu Deyu, Zhai Yongming. Zou Youwei.
Xu Ian, Zhang Xuqiang, Yang Yijiang
Ge Wenlong, Song Yongqiang, Wang Daxiong, Yang Ziguang Zhang Jianping.
Xu Ying Quan, Yang Shuli, Chen Yongsheng, Liu Junfeng Liu Fu Min.
Cut.
Dit, Ha Hyun-gi, Lee Moon-jung.
Shin Baejin.
Late production.
ZMCG.
Beijing Zhuma Chenguang Culture Co., Ltd.
dubber.
Dazy.
Music production.
The chief of the band, Cheng Xiaoshi.
Theme song, Hero.
Cheng, Spear.
Arrangement.
Ding Xiaokui.
Thank you, Mr. Wang Xiao, for the title of this drama.
Thank you.
Shandong Blumund Red Film Club. [National 4A Scene Area]
Henan Juntong Car Co., Ltd.
Jintang Jun Kin.
The Public Government of Shanzhou District
[Civil Government of Xizhang Village, Shanzhou District]
The Steel Jade Association in Shanzhou District
Shanzhou District, Temple, Village Scene.
Sanmen Mini City Pu Theatre.
Yuzhou, Zhou Jiajun Co., Ltd.
[legal consultant]
The legal consultant service unit.
Henan Lu Da Law Firm.
Special cooperation unit.
There are three Municipal Committee in total.
The People's Government
The PR Department of the Municipal Committee
The Commission of Shanzhou
The People's Government of Shanzhou District
Zhongtong County Commission.
The People's Government of Wenji County.
Henan Henan Boutique Co., Ltd.
Shanzhou Tunnel Cultural Responsibility Company.
Sanmen Cultural Tourism Investment Group.
Yang Tingxuan.
The guidance unit.
Learning to strengthen our country.
The circulation unit.
Qijin (Xiamen) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Control unit.
Henan Sandao Movie Development Co., Ltd.
[Joint Film Co., Ltd.]
[Joint filming unit]
The PR Department of Gansu Provincial Committee
Henan Provincial Radio Station.
Henan Provincial Literature and Arts Association.
Henan Film and TV Group Co., Ltd.
Beijing Times, Yishi Cultural Technology Co., Ltd.
Hebei Army Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Product unit.
Henan Elephant Film Production Co., Ltd.
[Qianzhou Cultural Development Co., Ltd.]
Qijin (Quanzhou) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
I'll reward Zhang Bing first.